{
    "id": "83c0501421df4cfbb8ed4aca5d81048b",
    "title": "English Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He was an audacious leader. He was ………………",
            "description": "Audacious means bold, spunky, courageous.",
            "answers": [
                "timid",
                "ruthless",
                "bold"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Why do you have such a belligerent attitude? The person’s attitude is ………………………",
            "description": "Belligerent means hostile or quarrelsome. ",
            "answers": [
                "benign",
                "friendly",
                "hostile"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The puritans led austere lives. They led very ………………………. lives.",
            "description": "Austere means abstemious. ",
            "answers": [
                "extravagant",
                "abstemious",
                "honorable"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Cats have an aversion to getting wet. Cats …………………….. to get wet.",
            "description": "Aversion means dislike. ",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "do not like"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "She gave him a baleful look. She gave him an …………………….. look.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "warm",
                "cold",
                "evil"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "It was a balmy afternoon. It was ………………………",
            "description": "Balmy means pleasantly warm. ",
            "answers": [
                "warm",
                "very hot",
                "very cold"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The pirates treated their captives with barbarity. They treated them ...........................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "cruelly",
                "kindly",
                "leniently"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "The benign uncle tended to spoil the child. He was ……………………….. to the boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "kind",
                "harsh",
                "cold"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "We took a circuitous path. We took a ……………………………. path.",
            "description": "Circuitous means indirect or winding. ",
            "answers": [
                "direct",
                "shortcut",
                "long winding"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The king loved to behave in a very ceremonial manner. He behaved in a ……………………….. manner.",
            "description": "Ceremonial means ritualistic or formal. ",
            "answers": [
                "formal",
                "liberal",
                "informal"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "It has been proved that fortune-tellers are charlatans. They are …………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "genuine",
                "foresighted",
                "tricksters"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Acid is caustic. It is ……………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sweet",
                "bitter",
                "corrosive"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        }
    ]
}